<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root>
	<技能 pt1="10" pt16="6" pt17="5" pt18="5" 互斥1="2" 介面="10501" 名稱="Life" 生命法術="是" 編號="1" 說明="Teaches you Life spells./c#F4F4F4 Allows you to learn and cast Life spells/c*. Each successful spell casting yields spell exp for improving the spell.\n\n/c#FFFFFFDamage done by magical spells will be increased by 4 instantly after learning this spell./c*" 魔攻="4"/>
	<技能 pt16="6" pt17="5" pt18="5" pt2="10" 互斥1="1" 介面="10502" 名稱="Wraith" 死靈法術="是" 編號="2" 說明="Teaches you Wraith spells./c#F4F4F4 Allows you to learn and cast Wraith spells/c*. Each successful spell casting yields spell exp for improving the spell.\n\n/c#FFFFFFDamage done by magical spells will be increased by 4 instantly after learning this spell. /c*" 魔攻="4"/>
	<技能 pt16="6" pt17="5" pt18="5" pt3="10" 互斥1="4" 介面="10503" 名稱="Chaos" 混亂法術="是" 編號="3" 說明="Teaches you Chaos spells./c#F4F4F4 Allows you to learn and cast Chaos spells/c*. Each successful spell casting yields spell exp for improving the spell.\n\n/c#FFFFFFDamage done by magical spells will be increased by 4 instantly after learning this spell. /c*" 魔攻="4"/>
	<技能 pt16="6" pt17="5" pt18="5" pt4="10" 互斥1="3" 介面="10504" 名稱="Earth" 大地法術="是" 編號="4" 說明="Teaches you Earth spells./c#F4F4F4 Allows you to learn and cast Earth spells/c*. Each successful spell casting yields spell exp for improving the spell.\n\n/c#FFFFFFDamage done by magical spells will be increased by 4 instantly after learning this spell. /c*" 魔攻="4"/>
	<技能 pt1="1" pt16="1" pt17="1" pt18="1" pt2="1" pt3="1" pt4="1" 介面="10505" 名稱="Curse" 大地法術="是" 死靈法術="是" 混亂法術="是" 生命法術="是" 編號="5" 說明="Able to reduce the casting time of spells great deal. The spell rank can be upgraded by casting Life spells, Wraith spells, Chaos spell or Earth spells.\n\n/c#FFFFFFDamage done by magical spells will be increased by 2 instantly after learning this spell\nEach time the spell rank goes up, damage done by magical spells increases by 1 /c*." 魔攻="2"/>
	<技能 pt1="1" pt16="1" pt17="1" pt18="1" pt2="1" pt3="1" pt4="1" 互斥1="12" 介面="10506" 名稱="Meditate" 大地法術="是" 心靈="2" 死靈法術="是" 混亂法術="是" 生命法術="是" 編號="6" 說明="Able to improve magical defense. The spell rank can be upgraded by casting Life spells, Wraith spells, Chaos spell or Earth spells.\n\n/c#FFFFFFMagical defense and fear resistance will be increased by 2 instantly after learning this spell.\nEach time the spell rank goes up, MP increases by 15 and magical defense increases by 1 /c*." 魔防="2"/>
	<技能 pt1="1" pt16="1" pt17="1" pt18="1" pt2="1" pt3="1" pt4="1" 介面="10507" 名稱="Hit" 大地法術="是" 死靈法術="是" 混亂法術="是" 生命法術="是" 編號="7" 說明="Able to increase magical power. The spell rank can be upgraded by casting Life spells, Wraith spells, Chaos spell or Earth spells.\n\n/c#FFFFFFMagical power will be increased by 2 instantly after learning this spell.\nEach time the spell rank goes up, MP increases by 5 and magical power increases by 1/c*." 魔攻="2"/>
	<技能 pt1="1" pt16="1" pt17="1" pt18="1" pt2="1" pt3="1" pt4="1" 介面="10508" 名稱="Staff Hit" 大地法術="是" 攻擊="2" 死靈法術="是" 混亂法術="是" 生命法術="是" 編號="8" 說明="Ablt to increase magical power and defense. The spell rank can be upgraded by casting Life spells, Wraith spells, Chaos spell or Earth spells.\n\n/c#FFFFFFAttack power increases by 2, magical power and magical defense increases by 1 after learning this spell.\nEach time the spell rank goes up, attack power, magical power and accuracy increases by 1 /c*." 魔攻="1" 魔防="1"/>
	<技能 pt17="3" pt5="2" pt6="2" pt7="10" 介面="10509" 名稱="Sword" 攻擊="4" 編號="9" 說明="Able to increase the attack power of swords./c#F4F4F4 Allows you to learn and use sword skills/c*. The rank can be upgraded by attacking with swords.\n\n/c#FFFFFFAttack power will be increased by 4 instantly after learning this spell.\nEach time the spell rank goes up, both attack power and accuracy increases by 1 /c*."/>
	<技能 pt17="3" pt5="2" pt6="10" pt7="2" 介面="10510" 名稱="Axe" 攻擊="4" 編號="10" 說明="Able to increase the attack power of axes./c#F4F4F4 Allows you to learn and use axe skills./c* The rank can be upgraded by attacking with axes. Attack power increases by 4 after learning this spell.\n/c#FFFFFFEach time the rank goes up, attack power increases by 1.\nAccuracy increases by 8 each time the rank goes up by 10./c*"/>
	<技能 pt17="3" pt8="10" 介面="10511" 名稱="Spear" 攻擊="4" 編號="11" 說明="Able to increase the attack power of spears./c#F4F4F4 Allows you to learn and use spear skills./c* The rank can be upgraded by attacking with spears.\n\n/c#FFFFFFAttack power increases by 4 after learning this spell.\nEach time the rank goes up, attack power increases by 1.\nAccuracy increases by 8 each time the rank goes up by 10./c*"/>
	<技能 pt17="1" pt5="1" pt6="2" pt7="1" pt8="1" 互斥1="6" 介面="10512" 名稱="Enhance" 編號="12" 說明="Able to improve defense. The rank can be upgraded by using melee combat abilities.\n\n/c#FFFFFFBoth defense and constitution increases by 2 instantly after learning this spell.\nEach time the spell rank goes up, HP increases by 12 and defense increases by 1. /c*" 近程攻擊="是" 防禦="2" 體質="2"/>
	<技能 pt17="1" pt5="1" pt6="1" pt7="1" pt8="1" 互斥1="18" 介面="10513" 名稱="Grapple" 精準="4" 編號="13" 說明="Able to increase attack power. The rank can be upgraded by using melee combat abilities.\n\n/c#FFFFFFAccuracy increases by 4 instantly after learning this spell.\nEach time the rank goes up, HP increases by 12, attack power and accuracy increases by 1. /c*" 近程攻擊="是"/>
	<技能 pt17="3" pt5="10" 介面="10514" 名稱="Shield" 編號="14" 說明="Able to improve defense. The rank can be upgraded by attacking with an equipped shield.\n\n/c#FFFFFFDefense is increased by 4 points, instantly after learning this spell.\nEach time your rank goes up, your defense will also increase by 3 points. /c*" 近程攻擊="是" 防禦="4"/>
	<技能 pt17="1" pt18="1" pt5="1" pt6="1" pt7="2" pt8="1" pt9="1" 介面="10515" 名稱="Reserve" 攻擊="2" 編號="15" 說明="Able to increase attack power and accelerate SP accumulation. The rank can be upgraded by using melee combat abilities or ranged attack abilities.\n\nEach time the spell rank goes up by 25, a SP Point will be yielded./c#F4F4F4 As the rank goes up, the SP accumulation will be accelerated. /c*\n\n/c#FFFFFFEach time the rank goes up, attack power increases by 1./c* /c#FFFFFF\nAttack power increases by 2 instantly after learning this skill./c*" 近程攻擊="是" 遠程攻擊="是"/>
	<技能 pt17="1" pt18="1" pt6="1" pt7="1" pt8="1" pt9="1" 介面="10516" 名稱="Finesse" 編號="16" 說明="Allows you to equip a two-handed weapon and increases attack speed. The rank can be upgraded by using melee combat abilities or ranged attack abilities. \n\n/c#FFFFFFAgility increases by 4 instantly after learning this spell.\nEach time the rank goes up, agility increases by 1.\n\nCan have a weapon equipped in off hand while equiping a sword, axe or hammer in main hand.\nWhile the both hands are equipped with sword, axe or hammer, attack speed increases by 10%.\nWhile having a bow equipped, attack speed increases by 10%.\nWhile having a spear equipped, attack speed increases by 10%. /c*" 近程攻擊="是" 遠程攻擊="是" 靈敏="4"/>
	<技能 pt18="3" pt9="10" 介面="10517" 名稱="Longbow" 攻擊="4" 編號="17" 說明="Able to increase the attack power of bows and stings. /c#F4F4F4 Allows you to learn bow skills./c* The rank can be upgraded by attacking with ranged weapons. \n/c#FFFFFF \nAttack power increases by 4 after learning this spell.\nEach time the rank goes up, attack power increases by 1.\nAccuracy increases by 8 each time the spell rank goes up by 10. /c*"/>
	<技能 pt18="1" pt9="1" 互斥1="13" 介面="10518" 名稱="Snipe" 攻擊="2" 編號="18" 說明="Able to increase ranged attack power. The rank can be upgraded by attacking with ranged weapons./c#F4F4F4 As the rank goes up, the chance for interrupting spell casting will increase. /c*\n/c#FFFFFF \nAttack power increases by 2 instantly after learning this spell.\nWith a ranged weapon equipped...\nEach time the rank goes up, attack power increases by 1. /c*" 遠程攻擊="是"/>
	<技能 pt18="1" pt9="1" 介面="10519" 名稱="Eagle Eye" 精準="2" 編號="19" 說明="Able to increase ranged attack accuracy and agility. The rank can be upgraded by attacking with ranged weapons.\n/c#FFFFFF\nBoth accuracy and agility increase by 2 after learning this spell.\nEach time the rank goes up, accuracy and agility increases by 1." 遠程攻擊="是" 靈敏="2"/>
	<技能 pt11="1" pt12="1" pt15="1" pt19="5" 介面="10520" 名稱="Collect" 採藥="是" 攻擊="3" 編號="20" 說明="Teaches you gathering skills./c#F4F4F4 Must have a pair of gloves or robot equipped/c* to gather something. The skill can be improved by gathering something successfully.\n/c#FFFFFF\nAttack power increases by 3 instantly after learning this skill. /c*"/>
	<技能 pt12="1" pt15="1" pt19="5" 介面="10521" 名稱="Fishing" 攻擊="3" 編號="21" 說明="Teaches you the fishing skills./c#F4F4F4 You must have a fishing rod or robot equipped/c* to fish. The skill can be improved by catching something.\n/c#FFFFFF\nYour attack power will increase by 3 points instantly after learning this skill. /c*" 釣魚="是"/>
	<技能 pt10="1" pt11="1" pt13="1" pt19="5" 介面="10522" 名稱="Dig" 挖礦="是" 攻擊="3" 編號="22" 說明="Teaches you mining skill./c#F4F4F4 You must have a mining pick or robot equipped/c* to mine. The skill can be improved by after obtaining something by mining.\n/c#FFFFFF\nYour attack power will increase by 3 points, instantly after learning this skill."/>
	<技能 pt10="1" pt13="1" pt19="5" 介面="10523" 伐木="是" 名稱="Lumber" 攻擊="3" 編號="23" 說明="Teaches you lumbering skill. /c#F4F4F4 You must have an axe or robot equipped/c* to lumber. The skill can be improved after obtaining lumber.\n/c#FFFFFF\nYour attack power will increase by 3 points after learning this skill. /c*"/>
	<技能 pt10="1" pt11="1" pt12="1" pt13="1" pt15="1" pt19="1" 介面="10524" 伐木="是" 名稱="Mechanism" 挖礦="是" 採藥="是" 編號="24" 說明="Able to improve the attack and defense while driving a robot. The rank can be upgraded by using melee combat abilities, gathering, mining, lumbering or fishing skill \n/c#FFFFFF\nWith a robot equipped...\nEach time, the rank goes up, attack power increases by 1; both HP and defense increase by 3. /c*" 釣魚="是"/>
	<技能 pt10="1" pt11="1" pt12="1" pt13="1" pt15="1" pt19="1" 介面="10525" 伐木="是" 名稱="Drive" 挖礦="是" 採藥="是" 編號="25" 說明="Teaches you to drive a robot. The rank can be upgraded by using melee combat abilities with a robot equipped, gathering, mining, lumbering or fishing./c#F4F4F4 While driving a robot, cannot cast spell and the equipped weapon won't work either./c*\n/c#FFFFFF\nEach time the rank goes up, load ability increases by 15.\nWith a robot equipped...\nMovement speed increases by 50% after equipping a robot.\nEach time, the rank goes up, both accuracy and agility increase by 1. /c*" 負重="15" 釣魚="是"/>
	<技能 pt10="10" pt20="5" 介面="10526" 名稱="Weapon" 編號="26" 製作武器="是" 說明="Teaches you how to make weapons. The skill can be improved by making a weapon successfully.\n/c#FFFFFF\nIt allows you to make swords, axes, hammers, bows, bullets, arrows and other weapons./c*/c#FFFFFF\nDefense increases by 3 instantly after learning this skill. /c*" 防禦="3"/>
	<技能 pt11="10" pt20="5" 介面="10527" 名稱="Armor" 編號="27" 製作防具="是" 說明="Teaches you how to make armor. The skill can be improved by making an armor successfully.\n/c#FFFFFF\nIt allows you to make heavy armor, light armor, gloves, helmets, shields and other armor./c*/c#FFFFFF\nDefense increases by 3 instantly after learning this skill. /c*" 防禦="3"/>
	<技能 pt12="10" pt20="5" 介面="10528" 名稱="Sew" 編號="28" 裁縫="是" 說明="Teaches you how to make clothes. The skill can be improved by making clothes successfully.\n/c#FFFFFF\nIt allows you to make robes, gloves, hats, cloaks, backpacks and other cloth armor./c*/c#FFFFFF\nDefense increases by 3 instantly after learning this skill. /c*" 防禦="3"/>
	<技能 pt13="10" pt20="5" 介面="10529" 名稱="Technics" 工藝="是" 編號="29" 說明="Teaches you technics. The skill can be improved aftery making products successfully by using this skill.\n/c#FFFFFF\nIt allows you to make staves, ornaments, robot parts and other products. /c* /c#FFFFFF \nDefense increases by 3 instantly after learning this skill. /c*" 防禦="3"/>
	<技能 pt14="10" pt17="3" pt7="2" 介面="10530" 名稱="ShadowBlade" 攻擊="2" 編號="30" 說明="Enhances melee skills and /c#F4F4F4allows players to learn stance 5 skills/c*. Attack to upgrade the skill level when equipping appointed weapons. If players never learn Grapple, the casting time of skills will be increased by 1 second. \n/c#FFFFFF \nLearn to enhance: Attack+2, Agility+2\nWhen players equip appointed weapons, \nAttack+1 each time when characters level up/c*." 靈敏="2"/>
	<技能 pt15="10" pt20="5" 介面="10531" 名稱="Cook" 烹飪="是" 編號="31" 說明="Teaches you how to cook. The skill can be improved by cooking something successfully.\n/c#FFFFFF\nIt allows you to cook foods with an additional ability bonus./c*/c#FFFFFF\nDefense increases by 3 instantly after learning this skill./c*" 防禦="3"/>
	<技能 pt10="1" pt11="1" pt12="1" pt13="1" pt15="1" pt18="3" pt19="1" pt20="1" pt9="1" 互斥1="33" 互斥2="34" 介面="10532" 伐木="是" 名稱="Mantle" 工藝="是" 挖礦="是" 採藥="是" 烹飪="是" 編號="32" 裁縫="是" 製作武器="是" 製作防具="是" 說明="Allows you to wear Light armor. The skill can be improved by fighting./c#F4F4F4 Your defense will increase by 3 points and your agility will increase by 1 point after learning this.\nEach time your rank goes up your load ability will also increase by 60 points./c*" 負重="60" 近程攻擊="是" 遠程攻擊="是" 釣魚="是" 防禦="3" 靈敏="1"/>
	<技能 pt17="3" pt5="1" pt6="1" pt7="1" pt8="1" 互斥1="32" 互斥2="34" 介面="10533" 名稱="Garment" 編號="33" 說明="Allows you to wear heavy armors. The skill can be improved by fighting./c#F4F4F4 The speed of shoot, gathering and spell casting will be reduced great deal./c*\n/c#FFFFFF\nDefense increases by 4 after learning this.\nEach time the rank goes up, load ability increases by 72./c*" 負重="72" 近程攻擊="是" 遠程攻擊="是" 防禦="4"/>
	<技能 pt1="1" pt16="1" pt2="1" pt3="1" pt4="1" 互斥1="32" 互斥2="33" 介面="10534" 名稱="Vestment" 大地法術="是" 死靈法術="是" 混亂法術="是" 生命法術="是" 編號="34" 說明="Allows you to wear cloth armor. Your rank can be upgraded by casting earth, wraith, chaos or life spells.\n/c#FFFFFF\nBoth defense and magical defense increase by 2 points after learning this.\nEach time your rank goes up your load ability will also increase by 48 points./c*" 負重="48" 防禦="2" 魔防="2"/>
	<技能 pt14="2" pt17="1" pt6="1" pt7="1" pt8="1" pt9="1" 介面="10535" 名稱="Avatar" 大地法術="是" 幻化="是" 死靈法術="是" 混亂法術="是" 生命法術="是" 編號="35" 說明="Allows players to move faster and possess avatars. /c#F4F4F4 Allows players to learn Stance 6 skills/c*. Attack or cast skills to upgrade the level when equipping appointed weapons. \n/c#FFFFFF \nLearn to enhance: Agility+4\nWhen players equip appointed weapons, \nAgility+1 each time when characters level up/c*." 近程攻擊="是" 遠程攻擊="是" 靈敏="4"/>
	<技能 pt14="2" pt17="1" pt6="1" pt7="1" pt8="1" pt9="1" 介面="10536" 名稱="Assault" 大地法術="是" 奇襲="是" 死靈法術="是" 混亂法術="是" 生命法術="是" 精準="2" 編號="36" 說明="Increases accuracy and agility. /c#F4F4F4Allows players to learn stance 7 skills/c*. Attack or cast skills to upgrade the level when equipping appointed weapons. \n/c#FFFFFF \nLearn to enhance: Accuracy+2, Agility+2\nWhen players equip appointed weapons, \nAccuracy+1 and Agility+1 each time when characters level up/c*." 近程攻擊="是" 遠程攻擊="是" 靈敏="2"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="生命法術" __value__="0x00000001"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="死靈法術" __value__="0x00000002"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="混亂法術" __value__="0x00000004"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="大地法術" __value__="0x00000008"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="近程攻擊" __value__="0x00000010"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="遠程攻擊" __value__="0x00000020"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="採藥" __value__="0x00000100"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="釣魚" __value__="0x00000200"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="挖礦" __value__="0x00000400"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="伐木" __value__="0x00000800"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="製作武器" __value__="0x00001000"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="製作防具" __value__="0x00002000"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="裁縫" __value__="0x00004000"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="工藝" __value__="0x00008000"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="烹飪" __value__="0x00020000"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="幻化" __value__="0x00040000"/>
	<成長方式 __name__="奇襲" __value__="0x00080000"/>
	<ALIAS attack="攻擊" capa="負重" con="體質" defend="防禦" dodge="靈敏" exclusive1="互斥1" exclusive2="互斥2" grow="成長方式" help="說明" hit="精準" icon="介面" id="編號" magic_attack="魔攻" magic_defend="魔防" name="名稱" skill="技能" spr="心靈"/>
	<DEFINE FALSE="0" TRUE="1" false="0" true="1" 不可="0" 可="1" 否="0" 是="1"/>
</root>